[Music]
Mr. Mohammad, is it you? Greetings to you. Yes, I am.
Greetings. Good evening, Professor. Hello. Good evening to you too. Thank you. Thank you. Professor. Please
draw me a schematic of a chord that is minor and becomes major. A chord
that is minor and becomes major. Yes, you can draw
me a minor and major chord.
We use the term minor-major now,
but then we wo
n't use it at all. Now, I
came across something in one of the pictures that I
sent you. I wanted to see how it would be.
Now, I asked you a question in the journal. I do
n't think it's time. You didn't answer. Yes,
you all
sent it this afternoon. Right,
9:00. I was sending it since morning.
No, let me tell you. Since 9:00, that is, the last day, I
sent about 100 to 150 things. I
was a doctor today and I didn't get to it, and I was all in Rome.
But I'll say, until the end,
stay healthy. 28th, right?
Yes, 28:00. Well, I
answered a lot, Mr.
You are Mohammad Shahi, yes, my teacher, I
am always asking you, teacher, we are all
here together, I am coming to Weiss. There is only
one problem. You are
very bad at zooming. Mr.
Naqi sent me one here and he, for
example, this second version you sent was good. Make the background
box a little
darker. This one is this. I wanted to
tell you. Yes, then, yes, my chart is a water. Now, it has a
date. Well, you asked for someone's service. I
read these two today.
Yes, my teacher, now Weiss is a minor major. I
want to know. When we have a king that
becomes a minor major, we
call that minor major turning into a violation, and that
becomes a violation. For example, a turn signal for us. No, no,
look, minor major is a term that has
been used, but how much?
Because
at the time it was used now, there was
no proper understanding of it. Later,
even then, we said that this
must definitely reach the opposite area for this to
come.  It can be used as a critique. Now you
think, here we have a king here,
right? Let's
put it here. Here
we have a king that is getting bigger and
bigger. The question is, is this
bigness a breach? That's
right, you're saying that. Yes, my question is,
well, look, bigness is not a breach, not every bigness is a breach,
because if you look, the price
hits the upper area and hits this low again
.
Right?   So
now let's use the terminology you learned this week
here.  One is
English,
yes, and the other is F,
right?  Well, first of all, the first thing that a person
breaks all these things that are behind, I do
n't know who is behind,
you know a dip first as an
OF,
right, unless there was an INGolf before it,
this is always said, they say you take
all the F, unless there was an INGolf before it, it had one.
Now, if we want to
take the bottom of the initial box, this INGolf, right,
where do we want the bottom of the initial box? I don't
understand exactly what you mean here, we want to say
this low, this INGolf,
this low, another break,
yes, no, is that right?
I think so, yes, now, when we have a
break from
above before it, we can no longer call it a break, that's the same ING that you have, you
say, well,
this is the ING because we
have a break before it, that is, a break above,
but this ING becomes the same reversal signal, right,
when does this apply, the ING that is here
and when the
price goes back to the  He's
rejecting this Golf you drew, so he can do his job and come back again, right?  Well
done, now it
can't always be this word that
will become this golf in the future. What are some things
to pay attention to?
One is, this is the one here,
if the custom package is within this range,
what is this here?
Can you tell me what this is?  This area,
if we have a Levi here,
a Lu here, one has broken this, this is exactly the
decision that comes on this decision, breaks it,
the price comes, sits on it and goes up
and comes under this. When this is the Levi,
this Levi that first comes here, this Lowe comes into
this area, it
has no reason to eat it again.
Right, when it has to order itself, so one
of the checks that means the check that we
have to do is whether the Levi that has formed here has
taken the order of that box, which
can be taken here. It has taken it right here. Yes, it has taken it
completely. So when it goes up, it hits the back of
this, it hits the back of this, it gives an in-golf
and when it comes under this, it hits this, that
is, this F should be answered later. They
use the term minor major here,
but it is wrong. Well, this can be done in
a way like this. We must first
see if the price has reached the larger area and when it
reaches that larger fish, we
must kill this Kinko, that is, now.  If the
price reaches here
and this order that is here is
taken and consumed, we will just come and say,
well, this is the box, we will
delete all of these, this one will remain, we will
say, this is the box that
brought the price from below, now it was the origin of the movement,
and when it returns from here, because this
origin is what is the loose,
loose, it is an F. Yes, a
type, a type of
this golf that after hitting
this high, it becomes this golf, here this below
becomes this golf, a type of Efe that becomes
this golf, the word is made like this, a
type of this, a type of Efe.
We have a type of F that is a
breaching F. Now we also have a type of F that is not
like a child, it wants to break, it wants to eat
in the area of ​​this, it becomes this
golf, that is, when it goes beyond this and
reaches the target, right, this bottom becomes the
limit, it becomes this golf, we will
talk about it in the next meeting, but now, to show me how to do a
minor major,
here is
our other teacher.  Now, according to what you are saying,
don't take the minor and major, but you
should take the major. You don't want to
take the minor anymore. If there is a minor here, you can see that
it will be a minor, but the major, as
you are saying, doesn't seem to hold the price in the reversal. So
what does it depend on if this low is a minor
here, has taken the order here, and it
falls below it? If not, some of the minors, this low
won't come, it will go higher.
Here, the major is not a major that is a loser.
This holds. The major is the same as the one that
has returned to its decision point. Yes,
then it holds. Yes, yes, when this
low hasn't taken this order and
comes here, it falls below it, and takes the order,
this low doesn't need to answer. It's not that
kind of insult. It's not that kind of violation.
When the price goes up, hit here.
This can hold and send it
up again.  Are you okay?  Yes, yes,
thank you very much. Please don't be a pain.
Now I'll draw
some schematics about this issue and
send them to you. If you don't mind, please let me know.  No,
the car in them is OK. Thank you very much. You
did me a favor. Master, please, good night. Do
n't tell me. Master. Eye. Reza. Good night.
Next person, number 24. Ghorbani.
Hello, Mr. Reza. Hello, Mr. Ghorbani. Well, do
n't be tired. Mr. Reza. I had a question. With
permission, I'll post my question in my journal. Excuse me, a schematic. Excuse me, a
schematic. If it
can be answered, give me one. Thank you. Can you
put it here?
Well,
which one can keep this price?
Blue
or green.
Arza. Its pair is considered a kind of decision.
Right? Yes, this is this color. This is a cumin. This is a
golf. Yes, this golf. Yes, blue can
keep it. Blue can keep it. So, if it
doesn't keep it, it can keep the price again in the future.
Blue.
If it doesn't keep it, it can keep it again in the future.
What does it mean?  That is, if he hits the green again,
well, come down again, this golfer
can hit it somewhere else again,
let me draw so that I understand what you mean correctly.
For example, think about it now, he has gone and eaten it in the green.
You mean, come here, hold it
right here, yes, exactly
here, this goat hits the back of this blue, this point,
no, this time he holds it first,
this time he holds it first, now, but
if he hits the back of this lip, but he holds it,
what you drew, look, this is now
hit twice, this blue, the way it was made, a stroke from above,
100, the first blue, he holds it,
right, you have it, then, then,
please, then, this hand is important, because because
this has come, it has violated here, here, the hand is important,
now here, if it does not have a kink,
here, if this green has been made before,
this green can also have the same reaction,
now why do you have a broken shot here, something like
this model in Char Arz, no, it
occurred to me, now to be honest, because we had two dips, I had a
doubt,
no, the first time, hold the blue.  The first
return from this lowe comes from
this lowe comes from here this holds
this blue holds
here should if there is a single candle stop to
stop go behind them thank you
thank you your hands are soft
please
which chat sir I have a question for you
fix a microphone come I have a card Mr.
Abbasi I'm sorry I don't know why it connects
thank you no questions Mr. Abbasian
fix this microphone this is your right it's going to be wasted
no
later we want to talk about this training
Kinga Rangi I want to
explain to you we don't have a color kink let me
explain here now you see Mr.
Abbasi I know you didn't go there watch that video
thing watch the troubleshooting video
here at least you can hear my voice tomorrow you watch this
about these mistakes you
made I will
explain to you we don't have a color kink in the chart we have a
lo why do we say lo rang
this so to speak not wanting anything new
lo green and lo red this lo green is a violation of lo
red oops and  Kings that are made before these,
so to speak, kings on the low and the
colored highs, these kings are important, that is, before they are
broken.
Suppose this low. Now we
consider this low as a low in the golf. A
kink that is important before the break
and
we expect this return from it.
Now this this this itself has a formula. There is a
formula that in the return we must be compared
to
[music]
That's it. Well, you understand this. That
means you understand. Write in the chat at least
[music]
[applause]
Mr. Naqim.
Well, don't be tired, Master.  Mr. Reza, do
n't be tired. Can I write a poem?  Yes, if
my picture came, tell me that my picture came, Mr.
Reza, your picture came, yes, yes, it came, yes,
this is the question of our friend that you also said to
ask you why you
took this place, and I will tell you this quickly first, then I will
ask myself this question. This is the kink, the time is
below, Mr. Reza, the time is 5
minutes. Well, based on this snare, I
drew this blue king. I said here, I said here, I said here, one
should be from the left of the area. It is possible that
this will fall in front of it, so that it becomes an oreg, but it
cannot be. Exactly, I did not see this left one at all.
I said yes, now I am from here, well,
here I have two to say, let me explain why, in
general, if I said something wrong, please clarify.
I had two here that my ones would
break here, and I will delete this now, to bring this
down, I
was cut off.
No, we're silent, we're listening. Sir,
my picture is gone, Mr. Reza.
No, this is it now. Your picture is now.
Yes, how do you know your picture is gone?
No, I came myself, something happened, it happened again, and it was like a
fall on Shah Reza. Well, here, I
have a kink, an important kink. The result of the failure is this one
DP for here. It goes up and hits the high.
This one becomes a DP. There was one before it,
why is it not high?
Well, I said the same thing. Sir, the result of the failure was
this high. The result of the failure was this high.
Throw one line from the top of my head. Throw one line
from the top of my head.
This is the top.  Oh, come on, now.  Well, let me
go to the lower part, which is more beautiful.  No, it's
clear here.
So you have this and that, and the first one is the
original.  That's right, the origin is
that other one, the origin of the big ones, from which I
am now, Mr. Reza. Now, I
took this, I said, hold it, it went up, it went
under this, this is the one, this is the
origin, this is the top one, I gave
this origin here, I gave this origin here, now this is my
main source, this is the origin that is here,
this was it, it breaks here, I mean, this
green box, my origin breaks this origin, this origin is my origin, my origin, my origin, so
can it be a
DP for me, do you understand what happened, I want to spend
some time here, no, this is it, oh, yes, it happened, oh, my father, yes, I know,
sir, this is the
internet, yes, unfortunately, this is what happened
to me, my DP, this is what happened, as the saying goes, it went
up, it broke, it went to DP, yes, after the
SNAR broke, I will delete this so that it
becomes quiet,
after this SNAR broke, the price returns
to DP, holds, goes up, okay?
This is my dip. Well, when I have my
main kink, this is my big kink. The discussion
is about where is the origin? This dip that I
held has gone up or reacted to it.
I will give this back. When I give this back, I will give it back.
Now I will erase it. It is thin here. It falls in the
1-minute time frame. I
have a single candle here. This is broken. Swap this. This is it.
And the price has returned. This is broken. I
will take this as the origin. I will
not take the top anymore. I will take this as the
origin. And
now I will bring it higher. The structure in the structure here
should be in the
structure. This is a reaction
there. Right now I will step. Mr. Reza. Yes,
wait. Who was Mr. in the structure? Our friend
asked the question. He was the second person. I
did not understand. Yes, now he
was the second person from the top. Yes, he was the second person.
Who was this Mr.? The
second person is the seventh black. I think because
38 started. Mr. Reza Mirza,
Mirza Ahsan, Mir Azimi or Mirzaei, Mir
Azimi, Mr.  It was Mir Azimi. Yes, look, Mr.
Mir Azimi. Now, I don't know if he is there or if he left. I do
n't know. Just let me say here. This pinkie that
is here should be returned to the structure.
Mr. Mirzi should be returned to the structure.
Why are you right? This is exactly in the
big structure. This has broken the roof. This should be
returned to the roof. Look, look, here. This should be
returned. If it doesn't return, it will go under this. Now,
I didn't see it at all, but it should be in
the structure now. When this is fixed here, come to this area. Now, show it to us. Let's see what happened. Mr. Reza played this golf. He gave the rebound, that is, the DP, that is, the original. Now, when these structures are formed, they should be
returned to this area. Now, the
timing thing is. Yes, I'll take the timing higher. Oh,
Dad, there's nothing
wrong with that.
Leave it here. Yes, I'm here. He's playing
golf. He's not playing golf under this box. The
original itself is playing golf. He's
going up from a higher level.  It's coming back, it's hitting
all of these. Yes, look here,
this Mr. Merzi, here, it should go back to this
edge. Why should you cut it right here? Mr. May,
Mr. Naqdim, now tell me where your card is. I'll tell you this.
Well, look, what you have here is the
box that Mr. Ney drew for me. Here,
if you move your time up, this is the
broken low range. When you move
your time down, this
and you make your time smaller and smaller, it
becomes this kinkin.
Basically, three of these
broke this low, this thin bottom.
Now, these three that broke here when
the price goes up, it goes up to the first one that breaks
here, but there's no return to the
inside. The second one is this, this should go back. The
lower area doesn't go back. It's
not worth it. It's going to hit
this area in the future.
When this comes back to this,
this is not the card at all.
That means this is enough. Come on, take the order below.
The origin moves.
The origin that you move your time up. This is
clear. This is tiny.  It is not clear that these
have a fractal that at that time if
this low comes, this area will be taken away,
we will draw this area itself, we will say
this is the origin, but this is possible, because it has not
returned down, it has the ability to be knocked down.
Professor Agha Reza, please tell me like this.
I wanted to say that Agha Reza, even if you take any of
these, whether you
take this or that one, now no, this is not possible,
but this lift is not this, Mr. Reza, this lift is not this, well, it is a lift. There is
a reason for this,
this has hit the back of this area, this is the lift, this is the lift, this is the lift, this is the
lift,
not that. If you want to take a lift, we
cannot take a lift from this, this has made us
barren to take a lift.
We take a lift where we have become barren
or have become a seller, but now based on the fractal,
I will tell you that the fractal is like this. Take your
time, cut it from here for a minute. Yes, well,
look here, I want this here, yes, this is the
lower edge of the line.  The bottom of the big fractal is here,
this kink
is smaller fractal again, this is why
this is important because the low itself broke this, this is the
last area of ​​the ramp, this is where the
first collision is, where is this, is this,
after the break, the price returned to the inner area,
this is not here, it was held again, it went
up again, did the
market return to the lower area after breaking this area, no, something is
clear here, when the price hit the top, it
left a mark here, who was
talking about it being hit below this? It was Mr. Omani, one of his friends, they
said, this is coming, this is a situation, I
said, yes, this is this, this is coming below this, it was me,
Mr. Reza, I was Bagheri, Mr. Bagheri,
yes, this is the same situation, Mr. Bagheri, you
think about this here, SN, the price is coming now, no,
of course, the one we are talking about was before this,
but this is coming below this, this is a
sign that
if it comes here at the moment, it will do it, but if it goes
above a level, it is
no longer worth it, that is, here, the width of this area is
no longer worth it to us, it should have returned to this low, it should have
returned.  You saw this when it didn't come back, it
hit its ceiling, then it came to this
area. If this low came,
you would see this area. Now, we are at the bottom of our origin, for example, like this.
Well, this is the answer to that question,
Mr. Azimi's friends. Sorry, Mr. Reza. I mean, the
reason why the origin here below
was more important now was that it had held
the price once, or that the orders here had
n't been placed so that the origin could change?  The order was
not issued here for the large structure of Origin to
take shape.  It's better to say it this way.
That is, if he held this position once, meaning
his order was emptied, Virgin would change
its place.  This is not this, if he came here, he would see
that the original place wouldn't change.
If you set your time to 1 minute, do it now,
do it for 30 minutes, sir,
do it for 30 minutes. Well,
we'll see it here for 30 minutes.
No, what is the origin for 30 minutes? Is this
origin useful for trading? No, because it didn't go
down in the fractal. If
it had gone down here, it would never have been
valuable.  This in itself was valuable.
What he was bringing here
was valuable, for criticism,
because we must finally
have a critical perspective on this. What if Mr. Reza,
excuse me, came and sat on the Ignore area
?
If that Lu, that Levi, that Origin 30
minutes ago that you threw a box, if the Lush
came, it would sit on the important Ignore area.
Still, we expected it to come
on that Kane, who sat for a minute.
No, no, he didn't
expect that Ignore's priority is more
important than this at the moment
because the Ignore moment doesn't let the price of an order go up, it
won't let it come in anymore.
So, did you get the answer to your question?  Please,
Mr. Abbasi, two or three people have come to the
microphone. Did you fix it, Mr. Abbasian?  Yes,
thank you, hello, I came with another system, sir. Okay, wait.
Now, Mr. T. Tell me,
Mr. Nagi, Mr.
Nim Miutia, brother
Miuty. Mr. Nagim, ah, ah, excuse me.
You said in your teaching session that we
have three types of DPs.
Of course, you didn't say any of the three. Before that, you
said that I have a kink that has held.
When it comes back and enters my box, it
gives me no loss. That's right.
Now, according to what you said,
here, this kink of mine has come down here. It has
broken the senate and
held. This kink of mine will be the last kink
that has come and leaked. And this will be
my green box. It will be a kink that has held.
A FL price that returns. It will form a kink above
this box. It will form a kink below this
box. And it will also form a kink before
exiting the whole box. Well, as we know, the
initial one will be 10 def.
Now, it will fall on this pink or
yellow.  It will return as long as it is on the bottom of
this golf. It is
on the pink
here. It is on the pink here. There is a kink here.
This pink is back. It is
used again. I don't want it to be on the top. It does
n't go up. No, unless this low has made a
level on the way it came down here.
For example, let's say you see this. If
that yolk is important, we made a hole here. Once it did, it
hit this. But that hole here or it has
become a hole on the way this low came.
Then the kink that brought the price to this
here gives soup. This is where the middle of this goes. At that
time, the yolk should be taken. Then the
yolk becomes important. This itself is not important. You have to
eat the price. Come, definitely. See with that yolk.
I will draw it. If everyone doesn't understand this,
look at it nicely. Look here or here. Draw it up. Let me draw it
here.
No, I want this to be your picture. Bring it up a little bit.
Your picture. Oh, look here. Think about it.
I am drawing from the green retracement. Well,
the price here has made a hole in the time
frame with here.  Hold it, it goes up, this one comes, it hits this one, it goes up, this one comes back,
you're
here, this one comes back, this one goes up,
then it comes here, it breaks this one, this one
comes here, it fixes it, it goes under this word, what does
this mean?  That can be yellow and red, you are
red and yellow, right? This yellow is the most important of
all of them. This should be your main order.
What is the reason, Mr. Reza? Because it has
created a hole. It is a hole. Yes, it is fractal. Yes,
if it does not have a hole, it will not be a hole. It is pink. Yes, it is pink. Okay, okay, let
me ask you this quickly.
Maybe some of them are related to the next sessions. If
that is what you say, for the next session and if
not much is going to happen, as the saying goes.
Now, let me take your time. We have a left shoulder
here. Mr. Reza, we have a DP. Well, in the
upper time frame, for example, I see this DP. In the
lower time frame, when I go to one minute and 30 seconds, the
DP is the same. The order transfer is in the form of
CP. Now the price
wants to return from here. You think that the price
has come down. Now, it wants to return up. Now
that it is returning up,
hit this CP. The whole thing up to here will pause.
That is right, that means there is nothing else here. This is what I have to
come here.  It has nothing to do with the kink I
drew here, right?
Well, let's leave it to the CP question. Why did you ask me
this question?
I didn't ask earlier, Mr. Reza. Sometimes I see a
kink. Well,
[music]
I see a kink that is the left shoulder like this. In the
time frame, for example, 4 hours, I see a kink. I see a
candlestick here
that coincides with the left shoulder from the left side. In the time frame
that goes lower, I see that
here, for example, it has come down in a compressed manner.
Now, this DP of mine is the result of a lift-lift. It's a
good place, but sometimes you see that it does
n't work. Sometimes you see
that it has come down like this. It's still very
possible. If the left here is below this
low, it should work. How else would
n't it work? Even if it's transferred like this,
even if the order transfer came down?
Order transfer doesn't make sense. These are the
ones you see. Let me tell you something. Order transfer is
not for these. These are tested.
This test is tested.  It can cause, for example, the
lower area to become the lower area to become the lower area. In
many cases, there is an
area in between that has not been tested.
Yes, it remains. Sometimes, the meaning of what remains
can work, but the ones that
come are not in our prioritization in this
compression. But if it is really a left left
ignore, as long as this low does not fall, it does
not make sense at all that it is ignored here.
Why do you expect the price to come from above to
buy this area, this will go below this,
so the stop has not yet hit, so you should
buy the stop so that this will be ignored,
which will hit the opposite, and come down on your head.
Mr. Reza, what I mean is that if this is
my kink that I am seeing here, its structure is 4 hours,
well, and the kink that I am seeing here is
a candlestick pattern or is it a
kink that I am clearly seeing in 4 hours,
I have to come from above here in these 4 hours, I have to come from
above here, I have to
come from above here, I have to be aware of this
golf, or should I come to a
lower time frame, this tracking order is
done here and here, no, I have to come and hit it, it has to come and
hit it, so as long as it does not hit
this, although it has come down in a compressed form,
so I do not take this golf, in
compression, in compression, we have a discussion that this is the
beginning of the end of compression, when it hits, the price
is allowed to reach this area, until the principle
goes beyond that, and then hit it until the price goes forward, but well,
this principle itself must also be hit
in order to go higher.
Okay, okay,
excuse me, this part, now this is the part, I
have an inglef here, I have a down inglef,
this is that this is low, now the price is going up, the DP is going to
inglef me, well, my
DP is going to inglef, I expect from Origin, either it will come lower or it depends on other things, it will go down, no, it will go lower, it will go lower, even if the DP is on this graph, it will go lower, it can go down if it hasn't reached the low itself, it will go down, it will go down, oh, these are the routers,
Mr. Reza, you asked, I didn't want to
ask about these either, but I saw it in the videos
because it comes up, I couldn't stand it for a night or two, I
said I should ask these sooner, now
if each of these is low, yes, this low time in the
video, it will be high, but this low
here, when it's behind this, it can go down,
yes, there is no reason, you
should have shown before
that this structure is in your schematic.  It's
wrong, I mean, if this wants to be F, it should be like
this. Let me tell you, it should be like
this. For example, come here, hit this.
Then this. This. This. It will be F. Even in the
lower structure, it will be F.
But if not, it won't be ten.
For example, come here, hit this. It can
hit this. Sorry, it can be like this. This. Come here,
hit this. Then come below this. How can
this be below this? Let me draw this. A. Up. This graph turns down. E. Go up.
Then come up. Now give the target below. That's
right, Mr. Reza. We will understand in the future
that this golfer sometimes comes down. Sometimes he also throws.
Sometimes he himself continues the same process. We know that
we are moving in the direction.
Sometimes he takes DP.
Sometimes he goes. LS. He takes this. What KDP takes.
KLS takes. You will understand
what depends on this. It depends on this
DP structure. Yes,
we will understand. Sir, if you want to
cut the video for too long, then I will stop after the
meeting. Now, some days.  Then I will ask if you want me to let
Mr. Abbasim go.
Yes, ask a question. Yes, let this
session go to Sunday. Were you in Group A? Yes, yes, the
group in the name of God. Greetings and good time
to you, dear friends and companions. We are very
happy to be with you with the new trading course of the
Zeus Group. This course will
be published in full in a dedicated playlist with the same name on the official Zeus YouTube page with the address Zeus Forex Channel, and all sessions
can be viewed in order from the first part.
In this course, you will see 9 one-hour teaching sessions
presented conceptually and practically
.  After watching each session, you can
practice and then watch 6 short half-
hour sessions of troubleshooting by friends who participated in the round
to get a better understanding of the
material. After that, enter the
next teaching session. To communicate directly with us
and use the troubleshooting plans, simply send a message to the
Telegram ID of Zeus Group Underline of this admin
and stay in touch with us.
Wishing you all success in your trading career, my
dears.
[Music]